{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Animal",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Which of the following is not a type of penguin?",
        "correct_answer": "Waterland",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Emperor", 
            "Chinstrap", 
            "Macaroni"
        ]
      },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Animal",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Walruses can eat about how many clams in one day?",
      "correct_answer": "5000",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "100",
        "130",
        "3000"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Animal",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "How many koalas stacked on top of one another does it take to reach the height of a male giraffe—the world’s tallest land animal?",
      "correct_answer": "7",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "2",
        "4",
        "50"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Animal",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which of the following animals is not nocturnal?",
      "correct_answer": "Sheep",
      "incorrect_answers": [
          "Skunk",
          "Leoard",
          "Tiger"
        ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Animal",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "An ant says, “Danger ahead!” by doing what?",
      "correct_answer": "Oozing chemicals",
      "incorrect_answers": [
          "Running toward water",
          "Rolling on its back", 
          "Squealing"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Animal",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Which of the following is not a type of penguin?",
        "correct_answer": "Waterland",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Emperor", 
            "Chinstrap", 
            "Macaroni"
        ]
      },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Animal",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Walruses can eat about how many clams in one day?",
      "correct_answer": "5000",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "100",
        "130",
        "3000"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Animal",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "How many koalas stacked on top of one another does it take to reach the height of a male giraffe—the world’s tallest land animal?",
      "correct_answer": "7",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "2",
        "4",
        "50"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Animal",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which of the following animals is not nocturnal?",
      "correct_answer": "Sheep",
      "incorrect_answers": [
          "Skunk",
          "Leoard",
          "Tiger"
        ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Animal",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "An ant says, “Danger ahead!” by doing what?",
      "correct_answer": "Oozing chemicals",
      "incorrect_answers": [
          "Running toward water",
          "Rolling on its back", 
          "Squealing"
        ]
    }
    
  ]
}
